(Sheldon:)And here's another
interesting weather fact.
Another? Great!
(Sheldon:)Changes in jet streams
can affect the speed
(Sheldon:)at which the Earth
rotates on its axis,
(Sheldon:)so bad weather can actually
make the day longer.
(Penny:)Well, there must be a hell
of a storm somewhere.
(Sheldon:)Joke if you must, but you're
going to miss these moments.
(Sheldon:)With Leonard home in a few days,
(Sheldon:)this was your last time
driving me to the grocery store.
(Penny:)You know, I will miss this.
(Sheldon:)I'll tell you what,
if my apples are mealy,
(Sheldon:)we'll hit the produce section
for one last crazy blowout.
(Sheldon:)Heck, you can even push the cart.
(Sheldon:)Please don't take my looking
forward to Leonard's return
(Sheldon:)as criticism of the job you've
been doing in his absence.
(Penny:)I won't.
(Sheldon:)That criticism will come later
in your report card.
(Penny:)Yeah, I didn't stay
for the detention,
(Penny:)I'm not gonna read
the report card.
(Leonard(in Penny's apartment):)-Hello.
-(SCREAMS) Leonard! Hi!
-Sh! Keep your voice down.
-Oh, my God. You weren't supposed
-to be here till Sunday!
-We finished the experiment early,
sol thought I'd come home
and surprise you.
(Penny:)Oh, my gosh,
why are we whispering?
(Leonard:)I didn't tell Sheldon
so we could have a few days alone.
-Oh! That is so romantic.
-Sure, that's why I did it.
(Penny:)I just cannot believe you're here.
Penny, it's your lucky day!
(Sheldon(off):)Three of the eggs are clearly
not jumbo. Grab your keys.